Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum H
Yale University Divinity School Library
United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum H
1927-2006
1993-1999
RG 11H
Yale University Divinity School Library
15
(42 boxes)
This record group represents a continuation of the official archives of the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia, supplementing and overlapping the papers in record groups 11, 11A, 11B, 11C, 11D, 11E, 11F, and 11G. It provides extensive information about the institutions and projects to which the United Board has lent its support. The United Board was established to support and coordinate the activities of Protestant colleges and universities in China. Following the Communist takeover of China, the United Board focused its efforts on educational work in other Asian nations. In recent years it has re-focused some of its activities on China.
United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the UBCHEA
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers.
Biographical / Historical
See the annual reports of the UBCHEA in the Library stacks for detailed information about its work during the period covered by these records.
Scope and Contents
The files have been maintained as sent by the United Board.
Arrangement
I. Organization and Policy Records, 1927-1993
II. Programs and Colleges, 1977-2006
III. Faculty Development Program, 1980-1995 >
IV. Collected Material, 1990-2004
Universities and colleges -- China; United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia
- Organization and Policy Records, 1927-1993; Series I
  - Legal Documents
    - Canton Christian College (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents
      Including regarding: Charter
    - Cheeloo Christian University, 1945-1957, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 2-7)
      Including regarding: Charters, University agreements, Constitution and By-lawas, Cooperating Board for Christian Education
    - Chinese Christian Colleges of United Board, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Including regarding: Charters
    - Chosen Christian College (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Christian College in China, 1933-1940 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Including regarding: Constitution and By-Laws of Associated Boards
    - Cooperating Board for Christian Education (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Including regarding: Certificate of Incorporation
    - Cy Press matter, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Including regarding: Annual accounting
    - Cy Press matter, 1993 Mar (Box OV-1)
      Including regarding: Continuing for the University of Nanking Accounts
    - Cy Press matter, 1969-1971 (Box OV-1)
      Including regarding: Annual Accounting, Petition for Annual Account
    - District of Columbia Law Governing (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Fukien Christian University (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - General (Box 2, Folder 15)
      Including regarding: Constitution and By-Laws
    - Ginling College (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Harvard-Yenching Foundation Inc. (Box 2, Folder 17)
      Including regarding: Certificate of Incorporation and By-Laws
    - Hangchow University (Box 2, Folder 18-19)
      Including regarding: Charter, Restoration needs
    - Hua Chung College (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Hwa Nan College, 1946 (Box OV-1)
    - Hwa Nan College (Box 2, Folder 21-23)
    - Hwa Nan College (Box 2, Folder 24)
      Including regarding: Republic of the Philippines: Articles of Incorporation, Financial statements, Curriculum
    - Nanking University (Box 3, Folder 25-30)
      Including regarding: Amendments to Constitution and By-Laws, Certificate of Incorporation
    - Nanking University (Box 4, Folder 31-35)
      Including regarding: Petitions agreements
    - Peking University (Box 4, Folder 36)
      Including regarding: The Constitution of Peking University
    - St. John's University (Box 4, Folder 37)
      Including regarding: Constittution and By-Laws: St. John University
    - Shanghai Baptist College and Seminary (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - University of Shanghai (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Second sequence legal documents
      - Cheeloo University, 1927-1933 (Box 5, Folder 40-41)
      - East China Union University (Box 5, Folder 42)
      - Fukien University (Box 5, Folder 43)
      - Ginling College (Box 5, Folder 44-45)
        Including regarding: Board of Directors: Constitution and By-Laws
      - Hangchow University (Box 6, Folder 46-47)
        Including regarding: Constitution and By-Laws, Forms
      - Hua Chung University (Box 6, Folder 48)
      - Soochow University, 1945-1971 (Box 6, Folder 49-50)
        Including regarding: Agreements, Charter
      - West China Union University (Box 6, Folder 51)
      - Yenching University, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 52)
      - Yonsei University, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 53)
      - UBCHEA, 1947-1977 (Box 7, Folder 54-58)
        Including regarding: Constitution and By-Laws (booklets)
      - University of the State of New York, 1964-1974 (Box 8, Folder 59)
        Including regarding: Minutes, articles, correspondence
      - West China Union University (Box 9, Folder 60-61)
      - Woman's Foreign Missionary Society (Box 9, Folder 62)
      - Yenching University (Box 9, Folder 63)
      - Yenching Women's College, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Committee Documents
    - China Concerns Committee, 1978-1982 (Box 10, Folder 65-68)
      Including regarding: Reports; Agendas; Correspondence
    - China Concerns Committee, 1980-1990 (Box 11, Folder 69-74)
- Programs and Colleges, 1977-2006; Series II
  - By country
    - Cambodia
      - Royal University of Fine Arts in Phom Penh, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 75)
        Including regarding: Proposals, grants, etc.
      - Royal University of Fine Arts in Phom Penh, 1997 May 15-17 (Box 12, Folder 76)
        Including regarding: "Workshop on University Curriculum Development"
    - China
      - Amity Foundation Teacher's Program, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 77)
        Including regarding: General correspondence
      - Amity Foundation Teacher's Program, 1997-1999 (Box 12, Folder 78)
        Including regarding: Teaching inquiries
      - Amity Foundation Teacher's Program, 1994-1996 (Box 12, Folder 79)
        Including regarding: Proposals, grants
      - Amity Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 80)
        Including regarding: Project reports
      - Amity Foundation Teacher's Program, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 81)
      - Amity Foundation/ NCCC, 1993-1995 (Box 13, Folder 82)
        Including regarding: Teacher payments, correspondence
      - Beijing Foreign Studies University, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 83)
        Including regarding: Correspondence
      - Beijing Foreign Studies University, 1995-1997 (Box 13, Folder 84)
      - Beijing Foreign Studies University, 1995 Feb 6 (Box 13, Folder 85)
        Including regarding: Visiting professor
      - Beijing Foreign Studies University, 1995-1998 (Box 13, Folder 86)
      - Beijing Foreign Studies University, 1995-1997 (Box 13, Folder 87)
        Including regarding: College English conference
      - Capital Normal University, 1994-1997 (Box 13, Folder 88)
        Including regarding: Proposal, grants
      - Central China Normal University, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 89)
      - Central China Normal University, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 90)
      - Central China Normal University, 1994-1996 (Box 14, Folder 91)
      - China Con-CZ, 1990-1994 (Box 14, Folder 92)
      - China Christian Council, 1989-1997 (Box 14, Folder 93)
      - China- IN to IZ, 1990-1995 (Box 14, Folder 94)
      - China Medical Board, 1991-1997 (Box 14, Folder 95)
      - Chinese National Science Foundation, 1994-1995 (Box 14, Folder 96)
      - Chinese Academy of Social Sciences, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 97)
        Including regarding: Tibet proposal
      - Christian Study Centre on Chinese Religion and Culture, 1988-1995 (Box 14, Folder 98)
      - Columbia University, 1988-1996 (Box 15, Folder 99)
      - Columbia University, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 100)
      - Committee on Scholarly Communication with China, 1995-2001 (Box 15, Folder 101)
      - Crane House Cultural Center, 1991-1997 (Box 15, Folder 102)
      - East China Normal University, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 103)
      - East China Normal University, 1994-1997 (Box 15, Folder 104)
      - Fudan University, 1995-1997 (Box 15, Folder 105)
      - Fudan University, 1995-1997 (Box 15, Folder 106)
      - Ginling Women's College, 1995-1997 (Box 16, Folder 107)
      - Ginling Women's College, 1993-1998 (Box 16, Folder 108)
      - Ginling Women's College, 1995-1999 (Box 16, Folder 109)
        Including regarding: Reports
      - Hangzhou University, 1994-1997 (Box 16, Folder 110)
      - Hangzhou/ Zhejiang University, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 111)
      - Hong Kong America Center, 1997-1998 (Box 17, Folder 112)
      - Hong Kong Institute of Education, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 113)
      - Hwa Nan Women's College, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 114)
        Including regarding: Dr. Davis's Reports
      - Hwa Nan Women's College, 1994-1997 (Box 17, Folder 115)
      - Jiangxi Normal University, 1990-1995 (Box 17, Folder 116)
      - Jinling Research Institute, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 117)
      - Maryknoll Fathers and Brothers, 1980-1999 (Box 17, Folder 118)
      - Nanjing Normal University, 1993-2002 (Box 17, Folder 119)
      - Nanjing Normal University, 1995-1997 (Box 18, Folder 120)
      - Nanjing Normal University, 1997-1999 (Box 18, Folder 121)
      - Nanjing Normal University, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 122)
        Including regarding: College English Teachers Training: General correspondence
      - Nanjing Normal University, 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 123)
      - Northeast Normal University, 1994-1997 (Box 19, Folder 124)
      - Qinghai Junior College, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 125)
      - Shaanxi Teahers University, 1995-1999 (Box 19, Folder 126)
      - Sichuan Union University, 1995-1997 (Box 19, Folder 127)
      - Sichuan Conservatory of Music, 1995-1997 (Box 19, Folder 128)
      - Tibet Development Fund, 1994-1997 (Box 20, Folder 129)
      - United Board, 1977-2006 (Box 20, Folder 130)
        Including regarding: Alumni histories; General correspondence
      - United Board, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 131)
      - United Board, 1982-1987 (Box 20, Folder 132)
        Including regarding: Christian relationships in China; General correspondence
      - United Board CEAIE, 1980-1991 (Box 20, Folder 133)
      - United Board, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 134)
        Including regarding: Policy re-establishing Christian colleges in China
      - United Board, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 135)
        Including regarding: Policy statement on unrest in China; General correspondence
      - United Board, 1995-1997 (Box 20, Folder 136)
        Including regarding: Publicity by others; General correspondence
      - University of Pittsburgh, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 137)
      - Whittier College, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 138)
      - Wuhan University, 1994-1996 (Box 21, Folder 139)
      - Wuhan University, 1994-1996 (Box 21, Folder 140)
        Including regarding: Correspondence; Proposals
      - Wuhan University, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 141)
        Including regarding: Xu and Kwei Scholarship
      - Xiamen University, 1993-1995 (Box 21, Folder 142)
        Including regarding: Correspondence, pamphlets
      - Xiamen University, 1994-1997 (Box 21, Folder 143)
      - Yanbian University, 1994-1997 (Box 21, Folder 144)
      - Yanbian University, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 145)
      - Yangzhou University, 1997 Jan (Box 21, Folder 146)
      - Zhejiang University, 1997-2003 (Box 21, Folder 147)
      - Zhengzhou University, 1995-1997 (Box 21, Folder 148)
      - Zhongshan Univeristy, 1992-1996 (Box 21, Folder 149)
    - East Asia
      - ATESEA (Association for Theological Education in South East Asia), 1986-1997 (Box 22, Folder 150)
      - ATESEA (Association for Theological Education in South East Asia), 1996-1997 Dec (Box 22, Folder 151)
        Including regarding: Scholars in Singapore
      - Hong Kong
        - Hong Kong Baptist University, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 162)
        - Hong Kong Baptist University, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 163)
        - University of Hong Kong, 1995-1997 (Box 23, Folder 164)
      - India
        - India Programs, 1991, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 165)
        - All India Association for Christian Education, 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 166)
          Including regarding: Annual report
        - All India Advisorty Committee on Higher Education, 1996-1998 (Box 24, Folder 167)
          Including regarding: Meeting minutes, reports
        - All India Advisorty Committee on Higher Education, 1995-1998 (Box 24, Folder 168)
        - All India Advisorty Committee on Higher Education, 1996-1998 (Box 24, Folder 169)
        - Ahmendnagar College, 1995-1998 (Box 24, Folder 170)
        - The American College (Madurai), 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 171)
        - The American College (Madurai), 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 172)
        - Arul Anandar College, 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 173)
          Including regarding: Proposals, grants, correspondence
        - Henry Martyn Institute of Islam Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 174)
        - Isabella Thobum College (Box 24, Folder 175)
        - Isabella Thobum College, 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 176)
        - Isabella Thobum College, 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 177)
        - Lady Doak College, 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 178)
        - Madras Christian College, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 179)
        - Madras Christian College, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 180)
          Including regarding: Project report
        - Madras Christian College, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 181)
        - Madras Christian College (Box 25, Folder 182)
          Including regarding: Special grant
        - Maduri Kamaraj, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 183)
          Including regarding: Grants, proposals
        - Mar Thoma College, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 184)
        - St. Anna's College of Education, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 185)
        - St. Anthony's College, 1997 Aug 14 (Box 25, Folder 186)
        - St. Anthony's College, 1995-1997 (Box 25, Folder 187)
          Including regarding: Denied proposal
        - St. Joseph's - Bangalore, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 188)
        - St. Joseph's - Bangalore, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 189)
        - St. Joseph's - Tiruchirapalli, 1995-1997 (Box 25, Folder 190)
        - St. Joseph's - Tiruchirapalli, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 191)
          Including regarding: Project
        - St. Xavier's College, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 192)
        - St. Xavier's College - Palaymkottai, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 193)
        - Stella Maris College, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 194)
        - Union Christian College, 1997 Aug 14 (Box 25, Folder 195)
        - Union Christian College (Kerala), 1996-1998 (Box 25, Folder 196)
        - Union Christian College (Kerala), 1995-1997 (Box 25, Folder 197)
        - Women's Christian College, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 198)
        - Women's Christian College, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 199)
          Including regarding:Alumnae Association
      - Japan
        - International Christian University, 1996-1999 (Box 22, Folder 153)
        - Kansai Seminar House, 1997, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 154)
          Including regarding: Pamplets
      - Korea
        - Ewha Woman's University, 1977,1995-1998 (Box 22, Folder 152,155)
        - Hannam University, 1997-1999 (Box 22, Folder 156)
        - Hannam University, 1995-1997 (Box 22, Folder 157)
        - Soon Sil University, 1995-1997 (Box 22, Folder 158)
        - Yonsei University, 1994-1997 (Box 23, Folder 159)
        - Yonsei University, 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 160)
          Including regarding: Medical Center
        - Yonsei University, 1987-1995 (Box 23, Folder 161)
          Including regarding: Underwood, Dr. Horace G.: Correspondence
      - Pakistan
        - Kinnaird College for Women, etc., 1984-1992 (Box 25, Folder 200)
        - Kinnaird College for Women, 1994-1997, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 201)
          Including regarding: Proposals
        - Kinnaird College for Women, 1980-2002 (Box 25, Folder 202)
      - Indonesia
        - Petra Christian University (Box 25, Folder 203)
        - Satya Wacana Christian University, 1995-1997 (Box 26, Folder 204)
        - Satya Wacana Christian University, 1996-1998 (Box 26, Folder 205)
      - Philippines
        - Asian School of Music, Worship, and the Arts (Box 26, Folder 206)
          Including regarding: Architectural design plans
        - Asian School of Music, Worship, and the Arts: Samba-Likhaan, 1992 Feb 2 (Box 26, Folder 207)
          Including regarding: Photos
        - Asian School of Music, Worship, and the Arts: Samba-Likhaan, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 208)
        - Asian School of Music, Worship, and the Arts: Samba-Likhaan, 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 209)
        - Asian School of Music, Worship, and the Arts: Samba-Likhaan, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 210)
          Including regarding: Proposalwith archiectural design
        - Association of Christian Schools and Colleges, 1995-1997 (Box 26, Folder 211)
        - Brokenshire College, 1994-1997 (Box 26, Folder 212)
        - Brokenshire College, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 213)
        - Central Philippine University, 1995-1997 (Box 26, Folder 214)
        - Central Philippine University, 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 215)
        - Inter-Institutional Consortium, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 216)
        - Inter-Institutional Consortium, 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 217)
        - Philippine Christian University, 1994-1999 (Box 26, Folder 218)
        - St. Scholastica's College, 1997 Aug 5 (Box 26, Folder 219)
        - Silliman University: Endowment Foundation, 1989-1995 (Box 26, Folder 220)
          Including regarding: Assets statements
        - Silliman University: Alumni Association of N.Y. and N.J., 1987, 1992-1997 (Box 26, Folder 221)
        - Southern Christian College, 1996-1997, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 222)
        - Trinity College of Quezon City, 1994-1997 (Box 27, Folder 223-225)
          Including regarding: Proposals, Grants, Project reports
        - Union Christian College- San Fernando La Union, 1993-1996 (Box 27, Folder 226)
      - Taiwan
        - Tunghai University, 1995-1998 (Box 27, Folder 227-228)
          Including regarding: Proposals, grants, project reports
      - Thailand
        - Mahidol University, 1994-1997 (Box 28, Folder 229)
        - Payap University, 1996 Sep 27 (Box 28, Folder 230)
          Including regarding: Endowment Fund (Kingshill)
        - Payap University, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 231)
        - Payap University, 1995-1998 (Box 28, Folder 232)
        - Payap University, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 233)
      - Vietnam
        - College of Foreign Languages: Vietnam National University (VNU) (Box 28, Folder 234)
        - Hue University of Education (formerly Pedogogy), 1993-1997 (Box 28, Folder 235)
        - Vietnam National University, 1997 Sep 18 (Box 28, Folder 236)
  - College Profiles
    - Ahmendnagar College (Box 29, Folder 237)
    - Chinese University of Hong Kong (Box 29, Folder 238)
    - Chung Chi College: The Chinese University of Hong Kong (Box 29, Folder 239)
    - Ewha Woman's University (Box 29, Folder 240)
    - Hannam University (Box 29, Folder 241)
    - Hong Kong Baptist College (Box 29, Folder 242)
    - International Christian University (Box 29, Folder 243)
    - Lady Doak College (Box 29, Folder 244)
    - Meston College of Education (Box 29, Folder 245)
    - Northern Christian College (Box 29, Folder 246)
    - Payap University (Box 29, Folder 247)
    - Petra Christian University (Box 29, Folder 248)
    - St. Christopher's College of Education (Box 29, Folder 249)
    - St. Joseph's College (Box 29, Folder 250)
    - St. Xavier's College (Box 29, Folder 251)
    - Satya Wacana Christian University (Box 29, Folder 252)
    - Seoul Woman's University (Box 29, Folder 253)
    - Silliman University (Box 29, Folder 254)
    - Sogang University (Box 29, Folder 255)
    - Soochow University (Box 29, Folder 256)
    - Soon Sil University (Box 29, Folder 257)
    - Sophia University (Box 29, Folder 258)
    - Trinity College of Quezon City (Box 30, Folder 259)
    - Tokyo Woman's Christian University (Box 30, Folder 260)
    - Tunghai University (Box 30, Folder 261)
    - The Women's Christian College (Box 30, Folder 262)
    - Yonsei University (Box 30, Folder 263)
    - Various Institutions (Box 30, Folder 264-267)
  - United Board Visiting Scholars program
    - China
      - Haixiao, Wang, 1995-2001 (Box 31, Folder 268)
        Including regarding: Nanjing University
      - Hongming, Zhuang, 1995-1998 (Box 31, Folder 269)
        Including regarding: Xiamen University
      - Hongzhe, Shi, 1995-1997 (Box 31, Folder 270)
        Including regarding: Yanbian University
      - Jianxin, Wang, 1994-1997 (Box 31, Folder 271)
        Including regarding: Sichuan Union University
      - Jinghuan, Shi, 1995-1997 (Box 31, Folder 272)
        Including regarding: Beijing Normal University
      - Jinyun, Sun, 1995-1999 (Box 31, Folder 273)
        Including regarding: Xinjiang University
      - Li, Xiao, 1993-2000 (Box 31, Folder 274)
      - Ling, Wang, 1995-1997 (Box 31, Folder 275)
        Including regarding: Huanan Women's College
      - Luping, Zhu, 1995-1996 (Box 31, Folder 276)
        Including regarding: Hangzhou University
      - Meilang, Xue, 1995-1996 (Box 31, Folder 277)
        Including regarding: Ginling Women's College
      - Ming, Zhan, 1995-1996 (Box 31, Folder 278)
      - Qinghuan, Shi, 1996-1998 (Box 31, Folder 279)
        Including regarding: Northeast Normal University
      - Qiuhai, Wang, 1995-1997 (Box 31, Folder 280)
        Including regarding: Capital Normal University
      - Shibin, Zhou, 1996-2003 (Box 31, Folder 281)
        Including regarding: Sichuan Conservatory of Music
      - Tianxing, Zhan, 1995-1997 (Box 31, Folder 282)
      - Wang, Tinghuan, 1993-1995 (Box 31, Folder 283)
        Including regarding: Asian Institute and Music
      - Wu, Yandi, 1995-1997 (Box 31, Folder 284)
        Including regarding: Fudan University
      - Xiaoqun, Ran, 1995-2000 (Box 32, Folder 285)
        Including regarding: Central China Normal University (Huazhong)
      - Xinmao, Zhu, 1995-1997 (Box 32, Folder 286)
        Including regarding: Beijing Foreign Studies University
      - Yina, Sun, 1993-1995 (Box 32, Folder 287)
        Including regarding: Suzhou University
      - Zhonghui-Xu, 1997-1998 (Box 32, Folder 288)
        Including regarding: Shaanxi Normal University
      - Zongmei, Shen, 1993-1995 (Box 32, Folder 289)
    - India
      - Babu, Mr. A. Chandra, 1996-1997 (Box 32, Folder 290)
        Including regarding: American College
      - Bhat, Dr. Mrs. Prema, 1995-1999 (Box 32, Folder 291)
        Including regarding: Stella Maris College
      - Christopher, Ms. Gloria, 1994-1996 (Box 32, Folder 292)
        Including regarding: Women's Christian College
      - Christopher, Kalaneethy Mrs., 1995-1997 (Box 32, Folder 293)
        Including regarding: Lady Doak College
      - Ernst, Ms. Lily, 1995-1998 (Box 32, Folder 294)
      - Flavia, Sr. M., 1992-2000 (Box 32, Folder 295)
      - John, Sheila Ms., 1997-1998 (Box 33, Folder 296)
      - Michael, Dr. R. Dinakaran, 1987-2000 (Box 33, Folder 297)
      - Nair, Mr. S. Chandra Mohan, 1994-1997 (Box 33, Folder 298)
      - Ruth, Ms. K., 1995-1996 (Box 33, Folder 299)
        Including regarding: Mandras Christian College
      - Samraj, Mr. Isaac, 1994-1996 (Box 33, Folder 300)
      - Samuel, Mr. Manohare, 1996-1998 (Box 33, Folder 301)
      - Sandhya, Ms. Kiran, 1994-1996, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 302)
      - Singh, Ms. Christianna, 1995-1997 (Box 33, Folder 303)
    - Japan
      - Yongliang, Shang (Box 33, Folder 304)
    - Korea